{
  "chapter": 9,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is advantage of dynamic scaling?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Resource capacity can be increased during run-time",
        "Resource capacity can be reduced during run-time",
        "No ‘system restart’ is required after resource capacity change",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Dynamic scaling facility in cloud has been achieved based on",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Resource virtualization",
        "Resource sharing",
        "Dynamic resource provisioning",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Can dynamic scaling approach be manual?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is the most fascinating feature of dynamic scaling in cloud computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "It is prompt",
        "It is automatic",
        "It is reversible",
        "It is infinite"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Predictable load patterns in cloud computing are managed through",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dynamic scaling strategy",
        "Proactive scaling strategy",
        "Reactive scaling strategy",
        "Static scaling strategy"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "In cloud computing, auto-scaling boundaries are set for a scalable system to",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Make the scaling effective",
        "Protect resources from external attack",
        "Minimize cost",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Distributed computing system architecture is apt to scale",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Horizontally",
        "Vertically",
        "Both horizontally and vertically",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Infinite scalability can be achieved through the implementation of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reactive scaling",
        "Proactive scaling",
        "Horizontal scaling",
        "Vertical scaling"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Better performance of a system indicates better scalability.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is the primary factor to limit scalability?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cost of system management",
        "Resource bottleneck",
        "Growing number of users",
        "Cost of resource components"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of scaling is more apt for distributed computing environment like cloud?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Horizontal scaling",
        "Vertical scaling",
        "A mixture of horizontal and vertical scaling",
        "It depends on the distributed computing architecture"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
